<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Best Voice Search</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="about_neat_roots"><u><b>About Us:-\n</b></u>At the heart of our digital journey lies the passion to bring people closer together through technology. This app was created by the visionary minds of Neat Roots and Neat Roots Bharat, who set out on a mission to build a platform that fosters meaningful interactions and simplifies everyday life.\n\n<u><b>Our Story:-\n</b></u>Neat Roots and Neat Roots Bharat are two dynamic organizations with a shared commitment to leveraging technology for the betterment of society. Neat Roots, a trailblazing tech company, is known for pushing the boundaries of innovation, while Neat Roots Bharat, an embodiment of Indian roots and values, strives to create solutions that resonate with the diverse and vibrant culture of the nation.Combining these strengths, we embarked on a collaborative journey to design and develop this app, where tradition meets technology, and where connections are made seamless. Our app is a reflection of our dedication to bridging gaps, bringing communities closer, and simplifying the complex in our fast-paced world.\n\n<u><b>Our Vision:-\n</b></u>Our vision is to make your life easier, more enjoyable, and more connected. We believe that every individual, every family, and every community deserves the best that technology can offer. With our app, we aspire to provide a platform that empowers you to navigate the digital realm effortlessly, connect with others effortlessly, and rediscover the joys of human interaction.\n\n<b>Also our team is dedicated to providing the necessary resources and training to enable 2 Lac individuals to become skilled in Android development by the end of 2023</b>.\n\n<b><u>Join Us:-\n</u></b>We invite you to be a part of our journey. Explore our app, connect with others, and experience the transformative power of technology fused with the warmth of human connections.\n\nNeat Roots and Neat Roots Bharat are excited to have you on board, and we look forward to shaping the future together.\n\n<b>Thank you for trusting us!\n\nTogether,we will build a brighter, more connected tomorrow.</b></string>


    <string-array name="languages">
        <item>Amharic</item>
        <item>Arabic</item>
        <item>Basque</item>
        <item>Bengali</item>
        <item>Bulgarian</item>

        <item>Catalan</item>
        <item>Cherokee</item>
        <item>Croatian</item>
        <item>Czech</item>
        <item>Danish</item>
        <item>Dutch</item>

        <item>Estonian</item>
        <item>English (US)</item>
        <item>English (UK)</item>

        <item>Hindi</item>

    </string-array>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <string name="go_ahead_n_we_will_listen">Go Ahead \n We will Listen</string>
    <string name="voice_to_text__hint">Voice to text here...</string>

    <string name="home_frag_title">Search smartly without typing...</string>
    <string name="button2_text">Voice to Text</string>
    <string name="button1_text">Voice to search</string>


</resources>